{"_id": "a808f265", "question": "I want to try the paleo diet, but it claims that potatoes are bad‚Äîand doesn't red meat cause strokes and other diseases?", "answers": "While many on the paleo diet do not eat potatoes, many certainly do. Often the level of starches/carbs is based on someone's goals and activity levels. Higher levels of activity = higher carb intake. Sweet potatoes and white rice are usually the go-tos but white potatoes have their place as well. Additionally there is evidence that white potatoes in the form of resistant starch\ncan be beneficial for gut bacteria.\nAs for red meat causing diseases (as many others have pointed out) this is nonsense. Don't determine your diet by what the headlines say is the latest superfood or what food is going to kill you. Its bullshit. Do your homework.\nThe paleo diet has never been about re-enactment, its a framework for living an optimal life based on human appropriate food, movement, sleep, etc. Over the past few years, the \"paleo diet\" has evolved to be more about real, whole foods than the previous strict dogma. Many folks have started including beans, potatoes, etc. based on their tolerance to these foods and overall health goals.\nFind out what works for you and don't get hung up on the minutiae."}
{"_id": "a474db54", "question": "A 4-stroke cycle diesel engine operates at 1800 rpm. The injector in each cylinder delivers fuel to that cylinder how many times every second?", "answers": "Hello there,\nInjections / minute = 1800 / 4 = 450 / minute, as there is an injection in 1 out 4 strokes, and, the engine is turning at 1800 revolution per minute\nInjections per second = 450 / 60 = 7.5, as there are 60 seconds per minute.\nHope this helps"}
{"_id": "5c12a38b", "question": "When I am drawing in Photoshop with a brush, it has this red line following the brush stroke while the stroke itself is lagging. How do I remove this red line?", "answers": "Go to Preferences > Cursor and uncheck ‚ÄúShow Brush leash‚Äù"}
{"_id": "895f1a82", "question": "Will drinking small amounts of red wine help if I‚Äôve had a stroke?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "591d986a", "question": "Is a droopy eye with red showing signs of a stroke?", "answers": "A droopy eyelid (ptosis) can be seen in Horner‚Äôs syndrome, which is sometimes caused by a stroke in the brainstem or by a dissection of the carotid artery (which can lead to stroke). Typically, there is no redness, however.\nA droopy eyelid associated with redness and swelling can be seen in cavernous sinus thrombosis, which may be a result of a life-threatening infection at the base of the brain.\nThis doesn‚Äôt exhaust the diagnostic possibilities, however. More common, and much more benign causes of redness (and sometimes ptosis) include such things as conjunctivitis, which has a variety of causes."}
{"_id": "25f0bb75", "question": "How do I find a home for a misjudged \"aggressive\" dog? My big baby barked at a dog with medical issues, and she‚Äôs stroked. I lost in court, and I‚Äôm afraid I won‚Äôt be able to act before the town‚Äôs time allowance before they have to intervene.", "answers": "Not knowing full story, it's difficult to give solution, however..\nCan you appeal Court's decision?\nHave professional references on dogs behalf?\nHave a few behavioral therapists evaluate dog?\nPost flyers around neighborhoods, churches, schools..\nLet family, friends, neighbors, teachers, co-workers, babysitters, know you're in desperate need *even if ‚Äútemporarily‚Äù..\nThink of every human that's ever been in positive contact with your dog and let them know your situation..\nCan you petition decision, OR any process like appealing, etc..\nNot sure of terms/conditions of whatever ruling they decided, however, does it vary In another county?\nThey have determined a dog that barked at another dog, or basically barked in general, is responsible for another dog with known medical conditions having a stroke? This does not seem logical and if this is their final decision they may be creating a huge number of issues.. Every dog that barks is going to be euthanized, sued, at fault in one way or the other if any dog within a 10 mile radius passes away, barks in return, vomits, etc.. Dogs bark, and they may Excessively bark.. That's what dogs do.. ü§î\nMaybe a video OR photos of dog can help others understand/visualize your dogs innocent ‚Äúaggressive-single-bark‚Äù that probably wasn't even directed at the other dog to begin with..\nIF your dog was determined ‚Äúaggressive‚Äù have a vet check him/her ASAP. Often infections may cause aggressive type behaviors and hopefully if you cure the cause it will resolve issue.\nIf your dog was at fault In whatever way, would other dogs owners accept payment plan, or some other offering, showing you nor to dog had bad intent towards their dog? (Sometimes money talks, unfortunately, but may save you from losing your pet..)\n?? I'm still stuck on dog that barked being at fault for another dogs stroke?"}
{"_id": "1b4f1166", "question": "Is red cell dist.width (in a blood test of CBC) can be considered as an indicator to stroke?", "answers": "In response to your excellent question, there appears to be some interesting data that tends to support this concept. By definition,, the red blood cell distribution width (RDW) is an employed parameter that represents the differentiation of red blood cell volume and size. (microcytic, macrocytic and normocytic). Results of the test, along with those of other blood tests, can help doctors to confirm the presence of certain anemias, a condition characterized by a lack of red blood cells. The RDW test can additionally determine, in many cases, the underlying source of the anemia. To cite one example, in the diagnosis of iron deficiency anemia, which is differentiated from folate deficiency, an RDW can be revealing. RDW would increase due to the release of immature RBCs in certain blood diseases. RDW tends to increase in iron deficiency anemia, as mean corpuscular volume (MCV) decreases. MCV is the average volume of a red blood cell. However, there is more to this research narrative.-\nIt has been claimed with some compelling evidence, though not thoroughly conclusive, that RDW had an interesting association to mortality prediction and cardiovascular episodes, such as acute coronary syndromes, ischemic strokes, peripheral arterial disease and hypertension. It is also believed that RDW can be a predictor of mortality in some patients with cancer, renal failure and lung disease. Cerebral infarction (CI) (ischemic stroke, 70% of all strokes)), with cerebral thrombosis, lacunar infarction, cerebral embolism are caused by a brain blood supply disorder of brain lesions. -It should be kept in mind though, that, there is really no direct biological marker to diagnose stroke. RDW might be an available alternative that can narrow the gap.-\nIn a more direct response to your curious question, current studies confirm that RDW is narrowly related to the occurrence of ischemic strokes. It has been observed that the levels of RDW in these stroke patients was higher than in those without occurring strokes. It is tempting and even logical to assume that RDW assessment plays a principle role in stroke progression, -\nAnother obvious question is how is RDW related to these mechanisms, and what exactly is causing these changes? The RDW biological mechanism between ischemic strokes and RDW is still a bit vague. There are many unanswered questions. Inflammation and oxidative stress (imbalance between the cell and its ability to rid itself of toxic metabolites), may play an important part in this dilemma. Inflammation lessens the survival ability of RBCs and causes cellular damage. Other studies say that RDW was associated with tumor necrosis factor receptors or C reactive proteins, and other inflammatory mediators, which are all inflammation markers.-\nIn conclusion, though, RDW thinly appears to be a predictor for mortality and ischemic stroke risk, though its mechanisms remain unclear. Inflammation as well appears to be a respected player in this pathological equation. Many of these research findings originate from a mixture number of independent studies (meta analyses). There is no doubt, that regarding this topic, we have glimpsed only the tip of the iceberg. WE must, and should consider the importance and relevance of all the other findings and observations before rushing to half baked conclusions. Let us continue to research, learn and properly heal, whenever we can.-"}
{"_id": "253c4b5e", "question": "Can Red Bull make you have a stroke if you mix it with alcohol?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "1bb139c1", "question": "If I have red spots after vomiting (petechia), does that mean my vessels are weak and I am more at risk for a stroke?", "answers": "I would advice you to visit a physician as soon as possible.\nPetechiae can be due to several causes. As you've mentioned capillary fragility can be a cause , but it's most commonly caused by platelet abnormality be it functional or depletion of platelet."}
{"_id": "cb0ef78b", "question": "In a death tournament with Batman‚Äôs death stroke, Damien Wayne, Robin, Red Hood, Red Robin, Nightwing, Batgirl, Batwoman, Heretic Raes al Ghoul, Lady Shiva and Bronze Tiger, how would it go and who will win?", "answers": "I don‚Äôt really understand the ‚ÄúBatman‚Äôs death stroke‚Äù and ‚ÄúHeretic Raes al Ghoul‚Äù, I am not doing to include Batman but I will do Deathstroke and I will include both Heretic and Ra‚Äôs al Ghul. I am doing to use Damian Wayne as Robin because in my eyes, I only really see four Robins and three is already on this list. I don‚Äôt know who is the Batgirl but I will use Barbara Gordon, just because reasons.\nSo Deathstroke vs Damian Wayne vs Red Hood vs Red Robin vs Nightwing vs Batgirl vs Batwoman, Heretic and Ra‚Äôs al Ghul, Lady Shiva and Bronze Tiger.\nSo first thing first I will take Batgirl out, just because I believe Deathstroke, Bronze Tiger, Lady Shiva, Red Hood, Nightwing, Red Robin and Heretic can take her out. And while she is highly intelligent, when you are in a death tournament, you can‚Äôt just sit down a plan. Damian Wayne probaby can‚Äôt defeat her but he does have a chance as he is train from both. I believe Red Robin can defeat her because he started his train when he was way younger. Batwoman could ‚Äúdefeat‚Äù as she have done so in Batgirl Vol 4 12.\nNext Batwoman will go down, just because usually her advantage is that she kills but now they are in a death tournament so she no longer gets this. Deathstroke, Red Hood, Nightwing, Heretic, Ra‚Äôs al Ghul, Lady Shiva and Bronze Tiger. Damian will have difficult with her but I do believe he can win as he is trained young and have is suppose to be ‚Äúperfect‚Äù. I see Red Robin being smarter and will think of a way out of this.\nThen I would say Damian Wayne is down, just because he is not as skilled and some more. He can be defeated by Deathstroke, When ever Robin is fighting Red Hood, Jason is not even looking for a fight, but one of a ‚Äúout fight‚Äù, Red Hood wins. In Teen Titans Annual Vol 6 1\nAnd this is what happen when Red Robin goes ‚Äúall out‚Äù in Red Robin Vol 1 14\nAnd forget when the New 52 movies say, Nightwing can beat Damian even without trying. In Batman Vol 1 688\nIn Batman Incorporated Vol 2 8, Heretic can defeat Damian\nI can see Ra's al Ghul, Lady Shiva and Bronze Tiger beating Damian in a a death tournament.\nFor a refresh, now there is Deathstroke, Red Hood, Red Robin, Nightwing, Heretic, Ra‚Äôs al Ghul, Lady Shiva, and Bronze Tiger left standing.\nWhen all of them, Heretic can go now. I believe that Deathstroke, Ra‚Äôs al Ghul, Lady Shiva, and Bronze Tiger defeat. As Deathstroke can fight a god, Ra‚Äôs have been around for a long time, Lady Shiva is the best of the best and Bronze Tiger is also good. While Damian might fail against in Batman Incorporated Vol 2 8\nI believe Red Hood, Red Robin and Nightwing is better than Damain Wayne.\nI would say Bronze Tiger goes out next. Deathstroke can take him, even though Bronze Tiger is more skilled, Slade has his ability and can use 90% of his brain. I also don‚Äôt really count Deathstroke the Hunted Vol 1 41 but if you do, good for you.\nI can see Jason beating Ben. Just cause Red Hood is more violent, in a way, and Red Hood is also very skilled as he is train by Batman, Nightwing, Bronze Tiger, Lady Shiva and the All-Caste. I believe he is smarter than Been. In Outlaws Vol 1 26, they did fight but it is good to keep in mind that in that issue Red Hood is not at his peak.\nRed Robin while may not be more skill, he is smarter in many ways. Bronze Tiger can be probably be defeated by Nightwing with difficulty. In Grayson Vol 1 18\nWhile Bronze Tiger is good, Ra‚Äôs al Ghul have been around for a long time. and Bronze Tiger have said that Lady Shiva is better than him. In Batgirl Vol 1 67.\nNot Ben is not to be taken lightly as he is very skill with Chi Manipulation.\nI will have to say that Red Robin have to go now. While, he is great at thinking and fighting, he might not be able to live though this death tournament. Deathstroke already can defeat him in Teen Titans Vol 3 4\nRed Hood already fight Tim and win a few times before and one of those times is in Teen Titans Vol 3 29\nNightwing will be able to beat Tim Drake, and they did fight in Nightwing Vol 2 139. It should be said that they both (Tim more) are not in the best of place. But you can see that Nightwing is not looking for a fight and is winning.\nWhile, Red Robin can out smart Ra‚Äôs, he did it with planing but with the same reason as Barbara, he can‚Äôt just think. And Ra‚Äôs should be skilled enough to defeat Tim. In Red Robin Issue 12\nWhile Red Robin did win aganist Lady Shiva\nBut if you think about Lady Shiva is not stupid and she won‚Äôt be falling for tricks, that is if Tim have time to plan against her with so many people.\nLady Shiva is good but I believe it is time for her to go. While she is good, Deathstroke has enhanced everything. And don‚Äôt believe the movie, Deathstroke: Knights & Dragons\nIn Outlaws Vol 1 26, Jason was was able to fight against Lady Shiva\nAnd while in Nightwing Vol 3 14, Lady Shiva did win, Nightwing was already injure before the fight, on top of that Nightwing did not even really use any of his weapons, besides the Escrima Sticks and two of his wingdings.\nBut Nightwing can land attack her still even if Lady Shiva can read his body language. Nightwing is suppose to be a unpredictable fighter and that‚Äôs what help him survive against Midnighter in Grayson Vol 1 6\nRa‚Äôs al Ghul have been around this earth the longest of everyone here. He have the most experience, he also have the Lazarus Enhancement, which help a lot in places like his strength, speed, stamina, agility, and durability. He can take on Batman, something Lady Shiva can‚Äôt really do.\nThe next person I will dismiss will be Ra‚Äôs al Ghul. Deasthstroke is better but not by a lot, while Ra‚Äôs al Ghul is the better fighter. In Deathstroke Vol 3 20, Deathstroke did seems like losing but I don‚Äôt believe he was in the right mind\nSo Ra‚Äôs al Ghul have a pretty big chance of winning but I am pretty sure that Deathstroke is stronger, faster, and smarter.\nRed Hood have defeat Ra‚Äôs al Ghul before in Outlaws Vol 1 27\nNightwing have defeated him in Nightwing Vol 2 152\nSo now down to three; Deathstroke vs Red Hood vs Nightwing.\nNightwing will now met his death because when you can comparing Deathstroke, Red Hood and Nightwing and ask who is the worst at killing, the answer will be Nightwing. While usauuly in a Nightwing vs Red Hood fight, I would back up Nightwing but this is a death tournament we are talking about. But in a in character fight, I would say Nightwing as he usually wins. In Batman: Battle for the Cowl Vol 1 3\nAnd when Nightwing goes against Deathstroke, it doesn‚Äôt usually go that well for Dick. In New Titans Vol 1 86\nGoing down to Red Hood and Deathstroke, the winner will be Deathstroke. While Jason is able to ‚Äúdefeat‚Äù Slade in Deathstroke Vol 3 16, he was already injure before the fight and in the fight Deathstroke did put up a really great fight.\nThis is just my long and sort of bias opinion."}
{"_id": "007d0115", "question": "I was for a few weeks in Sri Lanka and visited and prayed in the Nainativu Amanan Kovil. The Ayar stroked a cilinder-shaped red line on my forehead. What is the meaning of this Tilaka?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "f052a9be", "question": "Why does hormone replacement therapy raise your hemoglobin, hematocrit, and red blood cell counts, putting you at risk for stroke and heart attacks?", "answers": "Testosterone is believed to stimulate the production of erythropoietin which is a hormone that stimulates RBC production. Testosterone may also increase the number of erythropoietin receptors in bone marrow."}
{"_id": "2cb52546", "question": "After going red during heat stress, then white and clammy at heat exhaustion, what causes the skin go red again during the progression from heat exhaustion to heat stroke?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "1c325f94", "question": "Why does my red blood cell, hematocrit, and hemoglobin counts remain very high putting me at risk for heart attacks and strokes? How can I reduce the numbers?", "answers": "What is being described here is erythrocytosis. Before embarking on any work-up, I would review other laboratory chemistries with an eye toward determining if this result was artifactual as a result of dehydration. If so, the recommendation would be to drink more water, unless there are heart or kidney problems for which this recommendation would not apply.\nSometimes, what a patient believes is ‚Äúvery high‚Äù isn‚Äôt; without knowing what the entire CBC results are, this possible issue cannot be fully discerned.\nWhat follows is a list of possible causes of erythrocytosis. This is a partial list as I am sure there may be something I am overlooking, but at least this is a beginning from which a possible answer may come.\nI. Erythrocytosis associated with a normal or reduced red cell mass (spurious)\nAcute or chronic hemoconcentration (relative)\nSpurious polycythemia (also called stress polycythemia or Gaisb√∂ck‚Äôs syndrome)\nII. Erythrocytosis associated with an elevated red cell mass (absolute polycythemia)\nPolycythemia vera\nSecondary polycythemia (increased erythropoietin production)\n1. Systemic hypoxia\na. high altitude\nb. cardiac disease with right-to-left shunt\nc. chronic pulmonary disease\n2. Decreased blood oxygen-carrying capacity, increase in carboxyhemoglobin or methemoglobin (smoking)\n3. Impaired oxygen delivery, hemoglobin with increased oxygen affinity or congenital decreased red cell 2,3-diphosphoglycerate\n4. Local hypoxia ‚Äî renal artery stenosis\n5. Autonomous erythropoietin production\na. Tumors: hypernephroma, cerebellar hemangioblastoma, hepatoma, uterine fibroids, pheochromocytoma, adrenal cortical adenoma, ovarian carcinoma\nb. Renal disorders: cysts, hydronephrosis, Bartter‚Äôs syndrome, postrenal transplantation, renal artery stenosis, focal sclerosing or membranous glomerulonephritis\n6. Familial polycythemia due to autonomous erythropoietin production\nErythropoietin receptor mutations\nVHL mutations (Chuvash polycythemia)\n2,3-BPG mutation\nPHD2 and HIF2Œ± mutations\nThe use of anabolic steroids or recombinant erythropoietin; high oxygen affinity hemoglobins; sleep apnea syndrome; and hepatopulmonary syndrome are also possible.\nIf the diagnosis of polycythemia is established, it is an indolent disease with a median survival of over 15 years. The major cause of morbidity and mortality is arterial thrombosis. Over time, polycythemia vera may convert to myelofibrosis or to chronic myelogenous leukemia (CML). In approximately 5% of cases, the disorder progresses to acute myelogenous leukemia (AML), which is usually refractory to therapy. It should, therefore, be apparent that anyone with a diagnosis of polycythemia vera (PV) should be referred to a hematologist.\nCitations:\nBarbui, T et al, The 2016 revision of WHO classification of myeloproliferative neoplasms: clinical and molecular advances. Blood Rev. 2016 Nov;30(6):453‚Äì9. [PMID: 27341755]\nGreenberger, Norton J, et al. editors. The Medical Book Of Lists: A Primer Of Differential Diagnosis in Internal Medicine. 4th ed., Mosby, 1994. p. 145.\nHoffman R, et al. In Stollerman GH, editor: Advances in Internal Medicine, vol. 24. Chicago, 1979, Yearbook Medical Publishers, p. 260.\nJameson, J. Larry, et al., editors. Harrison's Principles of Internal Medicine. 20th ed., vol. 1, McGraw-Hill Education, 2018. p. 734.\nLee, G et al. The clinical and laboratory evaluation of the patient with erythrocytosis. Eur J Intern Med. 2015 Jun;26(5):297‚Äì302. [PMID: 25837692]\nPapadakis, Maxine A., et al. Current Medical Diagnosis & Treatment 2019. McGraw-Hill Education, 2019. pp. 530‚Äì531.\nResponses should be considered general in nature, and not specific to any one person; consequently, they are not to be construed as specific medical advice and do not create a doctor/patient relationship. For more specific advice unique to your particular situation, consult a local medical professional."}
{"_id": "b789e430", "question": "In carom if a red coin and its follow-up coin are pocketed in a single stroke, yet the follow has fallen into the pocket first and red second, is the red considered won or should another coin be pocketed to claim red?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "f38d4517", "question": "Death-stroke, dead shot, Rae‚Äôs al ghoul,Talon, and the herritic to kill Batman and Night-wing, Redhood, red Robin, and Damien would the batfamily win?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "7fc402ee", "question": "How can I get my 50cc moped to be stronger? I can't go higher than 50cc. I live in Italy and it has much troubles driving up in the mountains. It's a 2 stroke 3 gears Aprilia Red Rose 1992.", "answers": "You can go for a slightly bigger rear sprocket (+1 or 2 teeth) which should make your low end torque stronger. Although, you will lose out on topspeed in the plains."}
{"_id": "ac29cb4e", "question": "Is there a supplement or food you can take to minimize the number of red spots/bruises when you have to take a blood thinner to ward off stroke after atrial fibrillation?", "answers": "No. Anything that would counteract the anticoagulant therapy could easily result in death or permanent injury.\nDon't even think about it especially if it is because of cosmetic desire."}
{"_id": "e5e9d9ce", "question": "What could be a sign that could happen when I'm seeing yellow and red flashing signals why I'm watching TV or watching a TV show from a far away distance what could that be a sign of that mite happened a Stroke or what could happen?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "58e26fa0", "question": "The woman who I'm in love with placed her hand above mine today and stroked it. I got red and tried to took away, and she laughed. Did she think I'm a fool?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "4c575cfa", "question": "If the red and and the follow coin gets pocketed in the first stroke of the game? Should we have to pocket another follow coin?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "1dd76056", "question": "Do you think Union Home Minister's touted political master stroke ended in a double failure with new Jat vs Gujjar controversy protest with already add on sovereignty damage at Red Fort?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "438dcf3d", "question": "Do you think Union Home Minister's touted political master stroke ended in a double failure with new Jat vs Gujjar controversy protest with already add on sovereignty damage at Red Fort?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "9d33a2c0", "question": "Is a mountaineer, who spends much time in very high elevation, in danger of heart attacks and strokes due to thickening blood due to excessive red blood cell production?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "44562a0f", "question": "Is red cell dist.width (in a blood test of CBC) can be considered as an indicator to stroke?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "6940dd36", "question": "In a death tournament with Batman‚Äôs death stroke, Damien Wayne, Robin, Red Hood, Red Robin, Nightwing, Batgirl, Batwoman, Heretic Raes al Ghoul, Lady Shiva and Bronze Tiger, how would it go and who will win?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "b712188d", "question": "What Could possibly be problem with starting my old Aprilia Red Rose Classic 1998? We bought it Last year and We experienced some problems with starting it. We cant tell Why. Its a 2 stroke. Could it be old gas?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "5809e97f", "question": "I have penis head sensitivity. My foreskin doesn't go down. I tried to masturbate but after a few strokes it turns into a red ball, size shrinks down. I have never masturbated, I have had nightfalls though. What should I do?", "answers": ""}
